Wow! That was fun!
Wow.
An actual elephant bluefin tuna.
I just can't wait to cook it.
Huh?
What's up, Nami?
It's... the air. The air?
It's going to rain.
But it's so nice!
I'm sure of it.
Whoa!
Someone's on the execution platform!
Who the heck is that?
That old man said this is the
place where it all happened.
The king of the pirates
was executed right here.
He's there now? Yes.
We were watching the square as you had
ordered and he just showed up out of nowhere.
Perfect.
Let's go, Flash-A-Lay.
So, he finally showed up.
It took him long enough.
So this is what the King of
the Pirates saw when he died!
Captain Smoker!
Is there something wrong?
Come with me, Toshiki.
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down!
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals?
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on a cruise!
We are Hey, you up there!
Get down from there immediately!
But why?
You are standing on an execution platform
that belongs to the world government!
Now get down from there right now!
Now's not the time for such trifles.
Long time no see, Luffy.
I have been looking for you.
Now that's just rude.
Do you mean to tell me
that you, of all people?
Have forgotten my face?
Wow, she's absolutely gorgeous.
I've never seen such pure beauty.
Her skin looks so deliciously soft.
For God, I'm pretty sure
we haven't ever met?
Who are you?
I'll never forget you.
You were the first man who
ever truly struck me! What?
I never hit you?
What?
When you struck me with
your passionate fist,
it felt good.
Listen up, boys.
What would all of you say is the most
beautiful sight in the whole East Blue?
That would be you.
That's correct.
I am quite breathtaking, aren't I?
There isn't a man alive who
wouldn't crumble before my beauty.
But I prefer strong men.
Like you.
I'm going to make you all
mine, Luffy. Just wait.
Aw, gross. No way.
Just who the heck are you?
You still haven't figured it out?
This is the police.
Put your weapon down and come quietly.
I am placing you under arrest
for assaulting a police captain.
As for you up there, get
off that platform. Hold on.
Who did you say you were arresting?
We've got a big problem here, sir.
She's too beautiful.
I really don't give a damn. Arrest her!
Do we have to?
Can't we just stand here and look at her?
Surprise!
A terror is bombing!
Watch out, miss!
Did that just...
It slipped right past her.
Oh, man, that's weird.
That little stunt was dangerous, you know.
I'm flashily sorry,
but your smooth skin is unharmed, of
course, so there's no need for trouble.
Fairest Alvida.
Alvida?
I don't see Alvida.
Don't be so dense, you nimwit! I'm Alvida!
Are you sure?
Because I don't think you're her.
I guess I really did change
after eating the fruit called...
Smooth, smooth fruit.
No attack can hurt my skin
because it slides right off.
Unfortunately, a lowly fruit couldn't
improve upon my already stunning good looks.
One big change you may have noticed
was that I lost my freckles.
Sure, that must be it.
After becoming a whole new person, I
decided to join forces with someone?
who shared my goal of finding you.
Now that I've flashily made my entrance,
behold the real star of the show!
Monkey D. Luffy,
ever since the day you sent me flying,
I've been obsessed with
exacting my revenge on you.
That alone led me to
finally finding my crew.
My travels are an epic saga.
I went through hell, found friendship.
I even lost parts of my body.
I call this tale Tiny
Buggy's Great Adventure.
The first thing that happened was...
Why the hell am I telling you a story?
Don't know.
Now, what was your name again?
Buggy, Boogie, Beehe, Baggy?
Ah, I know!
It's Baboon!
Buffoon, you got a lot of
nerve, you rubber bastard!
And now Back the Clown is
going to make you pay for that!
Hey, that's Back the Clown!
Pirates!
It's the Back Pirates!
You people flashily stay where you are!
I want every single one of you to
see exactly how scary I can be!
Oh, yeah, buggy, right?
You mean you just now remembered it?
Hey, what gives?
Long time no see, you rubber freak.
How's your pal, Roro Noah Zoro? Got him.
Good job, Cabaji.
To all of my followers,
hundreds of billions of
them around the world,
we will now superflashily
begin the public execution.
Shut up.
You're trapped, Monkey D.
Luffy.
You can't move so much as an edge.
Tell me, Straw Hat, feel honored?
You'll die in the same place
as the King of the Pirates.
The barometric pressure is falling fast.
I've never seen such a sharp drop before.
You know, I thought I
felt something strange.
There's a storm headed
straight for the island.
A storm?
Yeah, we'd better hurry back to
the ship or we'll be in trouble.
Is it gonna be big? Hey.
Zoro! Where is he?
Have you guys seen him around?
You mean Luffy?
Pirates are here!
It's Buggy the Clown!
What'd they say?
I think they said Buggy.
and then what well sir
it isn't just Straw Hat
luffy it's also buggy
the clown and iron club.
Alvida they're all there
wanted pirates from
the east blue have taken
over our town square.
they do all of this
right in front of me why
those arrogant scumbags
captain smoker sir.
what are your orders send unit
number one out to the sea and
have unit number two surround
the pirates from the streets.
the rest will stand by within
shooting range of the square.
see that it's done sir and
give this order to unit one
they are to crush any pirate
ships as soon as they see them.
i don't want a single
one of those wretched
pirates to get off this
island not a single one.
it's
time
for the
execution buggy
the cloud who's gonna kill straw?
I had Luffy, yeah!
They're gonna execute him?
That freaking idiot. Let's go. Hold this.
Saint!
And treat it like a lady, you got that?
Come on, we gotta hurry.
Where we going, Nami?
The harbor, you numbskull. Harbor?
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
Captain Smoker, look.
Things are getting weird.
Hmm.
It's that kid.
What's he doing out there?
Well, if I didn't know any
better, I would say that Monkey D.
Luffy is about to be executed.
Captain, we are ready to attack.
Don't be hasty.
One pirate is about to kill another.
Let them fight it out first.
That'll save us the trouble.
Listen.
Once that Straw Hat loses his head, we
surround Buggy, Alvida, and their gang.
And do it fast!
Pirate Monkey D.
Luffy of the Straw Hats
will be flashily executed
for the crime of being stuck
up and making me angry!
Not living out flashily!
Oh boy, I've never seen an execution!
Well, you're about to, kid.
What?
Stop joking!
It's no joke!
All right, I hereby flashily begin the
festivities of this public execution!
I saw a massive stimulus
cloud in the eastern sky.
That means an unimaginably big storm is
headed our way and it's coming in fast.
If Buggy and Luffy have caused a scene,
the Marines are sure to come out.
And if our ship is washed out to sea
when we need to escape, we're done for.
That is a big deal.
As a matter of fact,
I bet the Marines have
already started taking action,
and they'll destroy the Going
Mary if they find it. Hold on.
So you're telling me the
Going Mary's in danger?
Come on, Nami, hurry up!
Wait for me!
Okay, men, double time!
Riding around on a Ritchie bike.
Who's that man?
Who, who, who's that man riding
around on a Ritchie bike?
Oh, yes, it's me.
So this is the rubber
guy's ship, huh? Uh-huh.
Would you look at that?
He's got a bigger ship.
He won't need it where he's going,
because it's almost time for
Buggy to flashily finish him off.
However,
just in case the rubber guy, who has
absolutely no chance of escaping,
happens to escape?
we need to burn this ship down.
Burning wood smells so good.
I'm so sorry.
Really, I am.
Please spare my life.
Why would I spare your life?
This is what happens
when you go against us.
I guess.
This is it for the man I had my eye on.
You've got quite a big
audience here today. Straw Hat.
You want to say a few
words before you die?
Oh, cat got your tongue?
That's all right.
Stay quiet or say a few words.
It doesn't matter.
You're still going to die.
Listen!
I'm the man who'll be king of the pirates!
What?
He's the king of the pirates.
In this town of all places?
That's a crazy thing to say.
We're finally getting to
the best part of the show.
Bye-bye now.
Stop the execution!
Now!
Saatchi! Zoro!
No!
It's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Zoro?
You made it, Zoro, but you're
just a little bit too late.
We're gonna break down the platform!
Boronor, Zoro.
Okay, boys, get him!
Let's do it!
Not even the Great Zoro can stop me now!
There's nothing you two can do!
It's the end for your captain!
Bastard!
If I can just cut down the platform...
Listen!
The moment Monkey D.
Luffy's head falls, we
all attack together!
Prepare for battle, sir!
Nami, hurry up! Nami! Heavy! Sorry.
But I'm dead.
Idiot!
Don't say that.
He smiled.
I'm still alive!
That's nice.
That was divine intervention.
Stop talking nonsense.
We gotta get out of this town.
Our troubles are not over.
Attack!
Surround all the pirates now!
Here they come!
Oh, wow!
So cool!
Everybody here went crazy so quickly!
Lupin!
Zoro!
We don't have time for this.
We've got to get out of here.
We'd better hurry back to the Going Mary
or we'll never be able
to leave this island.
And we sure as hell won't
get to the Grand Round.
Really?
Well, that's no good.
Run!
The Skrull Head gang is getting away!
Capture them!
Why did he smile?
Did he know he'd be saved?
No.
At that moment, he was certain
that his life was about to end.
He simply accepted death and
smiled after preparing himself.
Captain, we have to pursue the pirates!
Lieutenant, think back.
Have you ever seen any pirates who
smiled on the execution platform?
No, sir.
It doesn't matter how tough the guy is.
At the moment of death, they all
turn pale and die in despair.
That Straw Hat man smiled.
I saw it.
He smiled just like
Gold Roger 22 years ago
just like the old king of the pirates did.
On that exact execution platform.
Captain where's the
Straw Hat man now sir he
slipped past us and is
heading towards the harbor?
Unit 1 should have
destroyed their ship by now.
Well, sir, they had to return
to port for a refitting.
See, they couldn't light their
powder due to the sudden rain.
What?
But a reserve unit is currently making
preparations to attack the ship instead.
Captain Smoker, if we let them sail now,
they'll be able to get to the Grand
Line before we can capture them.
The wind is blowing towards the west.
It's a tailwind for that ship.
Is this just mere coincidence?
It's as if heaven itself has
special plans for this young pirate.
We'd better picket the
pace or we're toast!
I am White Hunter Smoker.
On my honor as Marine Captain, I
won't let that man leave this island.
What the hell is up with all this rain?
Nami was right about this storm.
If we don't get back to
the ship and set sail soon,
we're going to be stuck here for good.
You're wasting your time,
you silly little man.
There isn't anybody alive who can lay
a hand on this perfectly smooth skin.
That was weird.
I saw a field of flowers.
Captain Buggy, you're not
fried to a crisp! I don't die!
This isn't good, Buggy!
They're sending Marines from Headquarters!
They'll never stop!
Heh, I don't care, they
can stick their noses!
Don't let me say noses!
Ugh, my bad!
Huh?
What now?
We go after that little rubber twerk!
Moji and Richie are burning
his ship as we speak,
so he's got no place he can run to?
so all that's left for us to do
is do what Buggy pirates do best!
Kick his ass! Yeah!
Ha ha! Motor!
Yeah, Captain!
Chouchou buggy!
Bomb engine, ignite!
Set the ramp, now!
Right track is set!
No friction!
Smooth, smooth track!
Don't let those pirates escape!
Where did the smoke come from?
What is it?
Whiteout time!
Smoker!
I can't waste my time
with you little fools.
So strong.
So that's the power of
the Plum Plum Fruit.
He took out Buggy's entire
crew just like that.
Fire!
Smoker, you bastard!
I can't break free of
this horrible steel net.
Where'd they get a gun like that?
It's a cage shot developed by the Marines
to deal with Devil Fruit powers, cowards.
I'll get the Straw Hat.
Bring my billower pipe. Sir!
Dammit! Crap!
Why did it have to start storming now?
How am I supposed to burn
down this ship when it's wet?
Aw, man, Richie,
we're gonna get in big trouble if we
can't get a fire going in this rain.
One more try.
Relax, Ritchie, I'll feed you in a minute.
What are you doing?
Moji!
Well, if it isn't the little thief.
Go, Ritchie!
Special attack, fresh egg star!
Damn brain, it made my hand slip!
Richie!
I'll feed you later!
Good, now let's go!
Not so fast!
You have to get past me!
My name is Moji!
I am a proud buggy pirate, and I won't let
you get anywhere near this stupid ship!
Get ready to fire!
Marines!
Bad aim!
Fire!
Go contact the cannon unit.
We have to capture this pirate vessel.
Sir! Nami!
I know!
Damn this storm.
Which way is this sea? I don't know.
The rain makes it hard to
tell where we're going.
There they are!
Damn, they're like roaches.
You want to stop and fight them?
There's no time for that.
Oh, wow!
Who is that?
I didn't know you were
Zoro and a pirate as well.
Found one right here.
You lied.
You're just another liar! Oh, great!
What the hell did you do to that girl?
You never asked me what
my name was, did you?
So I never lied, did I?
You know there's no way
I'm going to allow someone
like you to leave town with
such a legendary sword!
Give it to me!
The Wadoichi Manji! Right now!
Okay.
What a jerk!
You can't fight a girl!
Get out of here.
Let's go!
Hey, Zoro, if you hurt her,
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Toshigi's got one!
I hate to disappoint, but you
will never get this sword from me.
I can't believe she's lost.
I've never seen her lose before.
Now I think it's time for me to go.
Why didn't you kill me?
I know.
It's because I'm a girl.
You're lucky, Zoro.
Being born as a man.
It's pathetic that you can't
fight me because I'm a woman.
It's embarrassing!
You may be physically stronger,
but you don't have the guts.
This sword isn't just for decoration.
I don't even think you know
what it means to carry a sword.
Would you shut up for one second?
Look, you got the same face as some
girl I knew who died a long time ago,
and before I know a thing about
you, you're talking just like her.
What I want you to do is stop acting like
some dead person you don't even know.
And try to be yourself.
Excuse the hell out of me.
It's not my fault I sound
like your dead girlfriend.
I had no idea it was so rude.
And thoughtless of me to be myself.
You jerk.
You ever think before you talk?
What'd you say?
I see the ship.
The harbor is up ahead.
Great.
Now what?
Straw Hat Luffy.
You're finally here.
Destiny.
Fate.
Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals.
Are held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
The Pirate King, fine by me.
I'm Captain Smoker of the Marines,
and I'm in charge of keeping
the peace in this town.
You're under arrest.
Huh? Arrest? Forget that.
See, I'm going to the Grand Lines so
that I can become King of the Pirates.
King of the Pirates?
And I refuse to get arrested in this town.
Then you'll have to go through me.
Let's go.
Sanji, I'll be right there. Go on.
Fire!
Get in, fire!
If we stay here even a minute longer,
the Going Mary will be done for!
You can't set sail yet!
Luffy and the others aren't back!
There's no other choice!
If we stay here, she'll be sunk!
Brightwater, fall!
What about the rest of them?
We'll pick them up later!
Don't let them escape!
After them! Nami!
Huh? Sanji!
Sanji!
Wait up, I'm back!
Where are the others?
Uh, who cares?
We'll just get them later!
Behind you! Look out!
Dammit!
This is endless!
We have to get closer!
But there's no way that we can take
the ship back against this current!
Goddammit!
Usai! Master!
Saint, ooze up!
What's happening?
I ate the gluten gluten fruit so my
body can be smoked whenever I want.
What's wrong?
Had enough already?
Come, come!
Kathleen!
Ah, crap, that's really gross!
My turn now, smoke screen!
Okay!
Dom-dom-pesta!
Don't you see?
You've got to go through me
to get to the Grand Line!
I told you!
You're not worth 30 million
berries your luck's run out!
I wouldn't be so sure about that it's you.
Hey, what's going on? Who's that?
How nice.
Now the government can have your head.
The world is still waiting for our answer.
Can someone tell me what happened?
Help!
Luffy!
Nami!
We gotta go.
The ship will be gone soon. Right!
Okay!
I'm gone!
What?
No, he can't!
I'm not gonna like this.
You're here!
That was certainly a
flashy gust of wind for us.
I have never been one to turn
down luck that's in my favor.
Where are we headed now?
That boy will face me.
There is nowhere he can run.
He won't stop till the Grand Line.
Go!
If that's what you want, then by
all means make your dream happen.
Why did you help that man?
Dragon!
It is not our place to come between
that man and his chosen path, Smoker.
Set sail.
We're going after him. What?
We'll enter the Grand Line.
But captain you you can't
abandon your post on
this island what would
command say tell them i Don't
care about orders i'm
coming with you sergeant
major tashigi i have to
hunt down roba noah Zoro
He's mine i will get revenge It
looks like she wants to capsize!
Hey, look! A light!
Is that a lighthouse?
It's one of the guideposts.
The entrance to the Grand
Line is somewhere ahead.
The Grand Line is somewhere
just out ahead. What now?
Do we have to go there in the middle
of a frickin' hurricane like this?
Okay then, I think we should say
something to mark the occasion.
Right!
Yeah, let's do it!
I'm going to the Grand
Line to find the all blue.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
The world's best swordsman.
I'm going so I can draw a
map of the entire world?
I guess I'm going.
to be a brave warrior on the sea.
And now, to the Grand Line!